spydialer.com 2019-06-05

# Privacy Policy | Spy Dialer

Privacy Policy Statement 

Effective Date: June 2, 2016. 

1\. INTRODUCTION 

1.1. PURPOSE OF POLICY. SpyDialer.com (“us,” “we,” or “Company”) is committed to respecting the privacy rights of users of http://www.spydialer.com (the “Site”). We created this Privacy Policy (this “Policy”) so you can understand our information collection, storage and use policies. 

1.2. OPT OUT. You may opt your cell phone out of being spy dialed, free of charge, by visiting out opt-out page. 

1.3. NOTICE CONCERNING CHILDREN. This Site is not targeted towards children under the age of 13 nor intended to be used by them in any manner whatsoever. Should you be aware of any child under 13 using the Site, please contact us so that we may terminate their account. 

2\. INFORMATION COLLECTION PRACTICES 

2.1. WHAT PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION DOES THE COMPANY COLLECT FROM SITE USERS? 

A. Categories of Personally Identifiable Information. We do not collect personally identifiable information for visitors that simply browse the Site. You may, however, seek to use certain services on the site. If so, we collect the following information as follows: 

i. Free Unregistered Users 

• IP Address, ISP, geolocation  
• Browser type  
• Device ID number (if smartphone app user)  
• Phone numbers spy dialed  
• Date/time of phone numbers spy dialed 

ii. Address Book Submission Users 

• Your email address  
• The content of your address book at time of submission  
• IP Address, ISP, geolocation  
• Browser type  
• Phone numbers spy dialed  
• Date/time of phone numbers spy dialed 

iii. Paid Subscription Users 

• First Name  
• Last Name  
• Email Address:  
• Password:  
• Address  
• Cell Phone Number  
• IP Address  
• Browser type  
• Device ID number (Smartphone app users)  
• Phone numbers spy dialed  
• Date and time of phone numbers spy dialed 

iv. 3rd Party Cell Phones Spy Dialed by Site Users 

• Date and time of request  
• Phone number spy dialed  
• Recording of outbound voicemail message from number spy dialed 

We also store email messages you send to us. This information may not be edited or deleted once submitted. 

B. Credit Card Information. We do not store credit card information you provide with orders. However, our credit card processing company authorize.net does. Their privacy policy can be seen at <http://www.authorize.net/company/privacy/>

C. Modification or Removal Process. If you wish to remove or modify any of your personally identifiable information, please login to your account and do so. Cell phone numbers previously spy dialed cannot be edited or removed. Said information in older data backups may not be deleted or modified. If you wish to remove your cell phone number from being spy dialed, visit our opt-out page. 

D. Privacy Policy Modifications and Updates. If we modify or update this privacy policy, we will notify you by posting a notice on the Site for 30 days. 

E. Effective Date: The effective date of this Policy shall be June 2, 2016. 

F. Browser Do Not Track Signals: California law requires that we disclose whether we acknowledge do not track signals issued by browsers should you designate such a choice with said browsers. We do not do so. 

G. Third Party Cumulative Tracking: California law requires us to disclose to you whether third parties can acquire and track your personally identifiable information through our website. Google, Facebook, Yahoo and Twitter can track you through this Site as we use their services for social media and internal tracking purposes. Google participates in the NIA opt out program. You can visit this [link](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/#completed) to view all companies including Google that track you and choose to no longer be tracked. You can visit the Facebook privacy page [here](https://www.facebook.com/about/privacy/), the privacy policy for Yahoo [here](https://info.yahoo.com/privacy/us/yahoo/details.html) and Twitter privacy page [here](https://twitter.com/privacy) to learn more about how these companies track you and use your information. To block parties from tracking you, try services such as the [Privacy Badger](https://www.eff.org/privacybadger) offered by the Electronic Frontier Foundation. 

H. California Eraser Law. We do not allow for the posting of user generated content on the Site. As such, the California "eraser law" does not apply to this Site. 

2.2 WHAT ADDITIONAL INFORMATION DOES COMPANY COLLECT? 

A. AUTOMATIC COLLECTION. Our servers automatically recognize and collect your IP addresses (the number assigned to computers on the Internet). No personal information about you is revealed in this process. We do, however, track how long you are on the Site, the pages you visit, your IP address, the results of actions you undertake, the keywords you use to find the Site and other information detailing your use of the Site. The Site may also gather anonymous aggregate data for all visitors that does not personally identify you, but that may be helpful for marketing purposes or for improving the goods services we offer. 

B. COOKIES. We may use standard first and third party cookies. You can choose whether to accept cookies by changing the settings on your browser. However, if you choose to disable this function, your experience at our Site may be diminished and some features may not work as they were intended. 

3\. USE AND SHARING OF INFORMATION 

3.1. WHAT DOES COMPANY DO WITH COLLECTED INFORMATION? 

A. PERSONAL INFORMATION. We use the personally identifiable information you submit to monitor and improve our site. We do not share your personal information with third parties with the exception of third party services that we use to run, maintain and analyze the Site. These parties do not market to you. We may use your personal information to track, identify and investigate illegal activity or violations of our terms of use. 

B. ANONYMOUS INFORMATION. We use anonymous information to analyze our Site traffic. We may use anonymous information in combination with personal information to track, identify and to investigate fraud or violations of our terms of use. In addition, we may use anonymous IP addresses to help diagnose problems with our server, to administer our Site, or to display the content according to your preferences. 

C. DISCLOSURE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION. We may disclose personal information if required to do so by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to (1) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Company or its parent company, subsidiaries or affiliates, (2) protect ours or others rights, property or safety, or (3) act under exigent circumstances to protect the safety of the public or users of the Site. 

D. ADDRESS BOOK INFORMATION. When a user submits their address book, we add the information to our website database to provide search results to other users. Specifically, when a user of our site submits a phone number or email address seeking to identify the associated owner, we may share the name of the person as it appears in your contributed Address book. We do not share your name as the source of the Address Book information. By submitting your address book to us, you transfer any and all legal rights to said information in consideration of being allowed to make additional spy dials. We reserve the right to store, use, rent, lease, and sell this information in our sole discretion to associated people/phone search services. At no time will the address book information be used for marketing or spam. 

4\. SECURITY 

4.1. SITE SECURITY. The Site has reasonable security measures in place to prevent the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information that we obtain from you. The Site utilizes a multi-tiered security system to prevent unauthorized access by third parties. Our servers are located in a high security, state-of-the-art facility with 24 hour per day monitoring. The site uses SSL security to assure secure transactions. 

5\. WEBSITE AREAS BEYOND COMPANY’S CONTROL 

5.1. THIRD PARTY WEBSITES. The Site contains links to other websites. We have no control over the terms and privacy policies of said sites. Please make sure to view the policies of those sites before providing personal information to said sites. 

5.2. ADVERTISERS. Advertisers and advertising networks like Adsense and Sovrn may use tracking code or pixels on our site pages to be able to serve ads and measure site traffic. As such, your I.P. address, pages viewed and device information may be shared with them. 

6\. CONTACT INFORMATION 

6.1. CONTACTING US. If you have any questions about this Policy or our practices related to this Site please contact us by accessing the “Contact” link at the bottom of each Site page. 

6.2 LEGAL NOTICES. Any legal notices must be sent to Spy Dialer, Inc., Attn: Legal Dept., PO Box 890370, Temecula, CA 92589
